gloinvest.net 2011-11-23

# GloInvest.Net

A. INTRODUCTION

GloInvest.Net respects your privacy and recognizes the importance of protecting your personal information. We understand that confidentiality is key in any financial relationship. We recognize that your personal and financial data is your private information, and we are committed to keeping it secure and confidential.

B. ONLINE INFORMATION COLLECTION

1\. Personal Information

You can visit and browse the GloInvest.Net website and find out about our services, check on opportunities, get a quote update, use our financial calculator, and access other information without providing GloInvest.Net with your personal information. GloInvest.Net collects personal information when it is voluntarily submitted by clients or visitors. This information is used by GloInvest.Net and its affiliates to offer you the highest level of service, complement our marketing and research efforts, and ensure compatibility among top browsers. Personal information may also be used in aggregate for us to learn about our Internet-using customers. Personal information you provide online is not disclosed to external organizations, other than businesses who provide services on behalf of GloInvest.Net.

2\. IP Addresses

GloInvest.Net Web servers collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address for the purpose of system administration and internal reporting of aggregate information. We use this information to improve our website, develop marketing, monitor website performance, and better meet client needs. When you request pages from our website, our servers log your IP address. Using IP addresses, we can determine the domain names of Internet service providers (ISPs) used to access the GloInvest.Net website. The domain names are not personally identifying, which means that -- with the exception of Account Access users -- a website visitor's session is logged, but remains anonymous.

3\. Cookies

GloInvest.Net website functions are based, in part, on your browser's ability to accept cookie files. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive. Cookies allow you to more easily navigate our website and customize website features that are updated each time you visit the site. For example, our website uses cookies to direct you to your financial advisor's home page and to help you build a personalized list of stock quotes.

Cookies also help us track repeat visits to the website. Most browsers are initially set-up to accept cookies. You may set your preferences to refuse cookies; however, this may limit your access to some areas of the website, and prohibits your use of Account Access.

C. LINKS

Our website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that GloInvest.Net is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other websites.

D. E-MAIL

For the purposes of improving our service and adhering to regulatory requirements, your e-mail communication may be reviewed, monitored or acted upon by GloInvest.Net associates including, but not limited to, financial advisors.

Because Account Access is a secure, User ID and password protected site, e-mail messages are secured using encryption while in transit. Messages sent on the public website are not encrypted.

E. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

GloInvest.Net reserves the right to change this privacy statement at anytime. Changes are effective to the Online Privacy Statement immediately upon posting to this site.
